They say, "The holy water's
watered down
And this town's lost its faith
Our colors will fade eventually"
So, if our time is runnin' out
Day after day
We'll make the mundane our masterpiece
Oh my, my
Oh my, my love
I take one look at you
You're takin' me out of the ordinary
I want you layin' me down 'til
we're dead and buried
On the edge of your knife, stayin'
drunk on your vine
The angels up in the clouds are
jealous knowin' we found
Somethin' so out of the ordinary
You got me kissin' thе ground
of your sanctuary
Shatter me with your touch,
oh Lord, return mе to dust
The angels up in the clouds are
jealous knowin' we found
Hopeless hallelujah
On this side of Heaven's gate
Oh, my life, how do ya
Breathe and take my breath away?
At your altar, I will pray
You're the sculptor, I'm the clay
Oh my, my
You're takin' me out of the ordinary
I want you layin' me down 'til
we're dead and buried
On the edge of your knife, stayin'
drunk on your vine
The angels up in the clouds are
jealous knowin' we found
Somethin' so out (Out) of
the ordinary (Ordinary)
You got me kissing the ground (Ground)
of your sanctuary (Sanctuary)
Shatter me with your touch,
oh Lord, return me to dust
The angels up in the clouds are
jealous knowin' we found
Somethin' so heavenly,
higher than ecstasy
Whenever you're next to me, oh my, my
World was in black and white
until I saw your light
I thought you had to die to find
Somethin' so out of the ordinary
I want you laying me down 'til
we're dead and buried
On the edge of your knife, stayin'
drunk on your vine
The angels up in the clouds are
jealous knowin' we found
Somethin' so out (Out) of the ordinary
You got me kissing the ground (Ground)
of your sanctuary (Sanctuary)
Shatter me with your touch,
oh Lord, return me to dust
The angels up in the clouds are
jealous knowin' we found